ED]
Good afternoon.
Hello.
I just received a little bit of this Hinoya's Can Zure.
Here you go.
They said they'd stop by and pick some up for me.
I want to eat it.
I'd like to eat it.
I'm sure many of you have seen this before.
Yes, I have.
This Italian burger.
It looks so good!
I heard he got it from the show.
That's great.
And also, this is something that hasn't been released yet.
Oh, wow.
What was it, from Yamagata?
Yamagata beef shank.
Yamagata beef shank!
Well, I got a can of something that hasn't been released yet.
I'm going to open it and let it warm up a bit!
Please do!
I'm visiting the Kino family right now.
The reason why I'm here is...
I went to the fishing port this morning.
Get on the room.
I asked the fisherman to give me a ride.
I took oysters.
Shell the oysters
Peel them off.
And then we went to KINOYA.
We each came up with our own oyster menu.
I'm waiting for them to make a can of oysters.
Now, I'm waiting for it.
Waiting...
You worked so hard today.
You worked hard.
Yeah, it was kind of...
I had a busy working day.
And I woke up early in the morning.
Working people don't get up this early.
What time did you get up?
I got up at 2:30.
I got up at 3:00.
And then you came out.
I heard a lot about it.
It was so cold at the fishing port.
I thought my feet would freeze.
I heard that yesterday and today were the coldest days of the year.
I was a little unlucky.
But it was fun.
It was fun.
The scenery was beautiful.
It's the first time I've been in the ocean like that.
On the ocean.
And eating oysters like that.
I didn't know that.
It's like a string.
Yeah, there was a lot of string on it.
They were attached.
And then we'd peel them off the oysters, and we'd get behind them.
It was fun to peel.
It was so much fun, you should try it too!
It was a lot of fun.
It was pretty hard work, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was fun.
Now, I'm having the oysters canned.
I'm having them canned.
They look so good, so I'm looking forward to it.
You know, you have to measure it out.
How many grams, how many grams.
I did it.
And then just now...
I was in the factory.
I was wearing something white.
I lost my bangs.
Yeah, I was completely...
All white.
And the hat.
I'm a factory worker now.
You know, when I was in elementary school.
You know, like a factory tour?
I didn't have one. It was my first time.
It reminds me of that.
The garbage?
Yeah, I'll go.
I think we'll just go to the garbage.
Oh, really?
No cars or anything?
No.
I'm new to food.
Enoki mushrooms?
I'd like to go to the mountains and bury shiitake mushrooms.
What about that? What about rice?
There is rice again, isn't there? I ate some.
I think it's a common thing for people in the Tohoku region. I don't think people in Kanto and Kansai have it.
That's true. We ate it.
The rice paddies are amazing.
Hello. Wind in the legs. It was amazing.Hello. Wind in the legs. It was awesome.
I missed it.
It was my first factory.
You went to Thailand recently.
Yeah.
We've been meeting all the time.
All the time.
We've been seeing each other for about 20 days.
We saw each other in Thailand, too, so it's even more...
Yeah.
Thailand was warm, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was summer.
It was nice.
Aren't you sweating? The heat.
Uh, yeah, a little bit, but it was hot.
Yeah, it's hot. It's summer.
Yeah, it's summer here.
It's summer.
But it was a lot less humid than I thought it would be.
Bouquet was fun.
Yeah, bouquet is nice.
But honey tan...
Here it comes!
Wow!
Wow! Yay!
Wow! Wow!
That looks so delicious!
I'm so happy!
It's warm! Can you see it?
This one?
What's this?
That's Yamagata beef shank.
Yamagata beef shank.
This one too!
It smells so good!
It's warm!
Ah! This is the hamburger
The hamburger that stole the show!
Ta-da!
Hamburgers.
Smells so good!
Looks so delicious!
Since we're here, let's start with the new item
I'm going to eat it!
I'm so happy!
It's such a new product.
I can eat it!
Yay! After you.
Yay!
After you.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
Looks so delicious!
So soft!
soft and flaky
Bon appétit!
Thank you for the food!
Is it good?
Yes, it's delicious!
It's so good!
The meat is so tender.
I want some rice.
Sweet and tender.
It's so good!
I updated my canned yakitori yesterday.
I think this might be the best.
Really? I know. I know.
It's delicious.
It's so good.
It's warm.
Thank you.
I want to eat rice.
It tastes like rice.
Do you want a hamburger too?
Sure.
Thank you.
Smells good. Tomatoes.
Good evening.
Bon appétit.
Mmm, delicious.
Delicious!
This tomato sauce thing is so good!
Really?
Yes, it is.
I love tomatoes.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
Yum.
Oh, this is delicious.
Delicious.
It's amazing how good the third flavor is.
Oh, yeah, for sure.
Hey.
I don't eat canned food much, but I started eating it at Ki no Ya.
Delicious.
What was that? What were we talking about?What was that? What were we talking about?
Thailand?
Thailand.
And we brought a lot of Japanese food.
Should I have brought canned food? You're right.
I didn't think of that.
Did you bring some packaged rice?
I had packaged rice and miso soup, but no side dishes.
I thought it would be a nice side dish.
Canned food.
Yeah, next time we go somewhere...
You want me to bring canned food? Let's bring some canned food.
I want to bring this.
I want to take it with me.
The mandarins have been in the same room for a long time.
That's right.
We ate rice in the middle of the night.
They came home late.
He came home late, but...
But I was hungry.
So while one of us showered.
The rest of us ate from packets of rice.
But the others in the room didn't seem to eat that much.
You know...
But you got up in the morning and went to eat.
You were slammed when you left the room.
You were, weren't you?
This is delicious.
It's so good!
And we go to Thailand and see each other every day.
We see each other every day.
I've been briefed on what we're going to do a little bit at a time on the national tour.
I've been getting explanations about what we're going to do.
The other day we took a lesson.
It was a new space for me.
But there were a lot of things that seemed new and difficult
There were a lot of things that seemed to be difficult.
You mean, it seemed...
That's right.
By the way, it started when this video was uploaded.
Oh, wow.
It's started.
It has?
Yeah.
It's just... we got through the last tour, so...
I feel a little more relaxed.
Yeah.
Maybe it's because I've only been taught a little bit since the tour started.
Maybe it's because I've only been told a little bit about it.
By the time you're looking at this, you might know what it's all about.
But right now, we're still...
We've only seen the beginning.
We only know how to do it.
But you know... you only know the beginning.
I can remember that much.
Hey...
The rest is a little...
It's scary, isn't it?
It'll be fun.
I'm looking forward to it.
What prefecture are you looking forward to?
Hmmm...
Mmm~
Yeah.
I don't know about you, but this is my first time in Chiba.
Is it?
Huh? Chiba is big.
I think so.
Oh, wow.
That's for sure.
I went to Hiroshima once.
Not at all.
That's right.
Just Mamiji Manju.
It ended with the concert and mamiji manju.
I'm looking forward to Hokkaido.
Hokkaido is kind of...
It's delicious, isn't it?
Yes, it's really good.
No matter how many times I go there, it's always delicious.
I can't forget the melon parfait.
What's Hakkouda?
That's a train station, right?
Yeah, it's a train station.
Like the café near the station.
I'll never forget it.
It's good, right?
It was delicious.
I wonder where else it is.
I want to eat that. Long rice cakes.
Oh, right. That's right. I heard it's in Nagasaki.
What's that?
Choumochi, in Nagoya... Nagoya, right?
When I went to Nagoya, I was looking for souvenirs.
And they were selling something called "nagamochi".
I happened to see a video of my favorite Korean idols eating them.
I found it.That's what I found.
I thought, "What, they sell them? I thought.
I thought, "Chomochi is a kind of rice cake made in Nagoya.
I bought it. I bought it, and it was so delicious.
It was so delicious that I gave it to Miyu and my boyfriend who were with me at the time.
I gave it to Miyu and my boyfriend, who were with me at the time, and they said they would definitely buy it next time, and that they would definitely go to Nagoya for it.
But I found out later that Nagamochi is a Nagasaki specialty.
I wonder why it was there.
I wonder if there are other places around there.
They are so delicious.
I really like the happiness mode.
Yes, I like it.
I want to eat long rice cakes.
It's so good.
I'll buy some next time.
I'll buy it next time. I'll definitely buy it.
Oh, please buy them after you and Ri buy them.
They'll run out.
They'll give it a name.
That's not a good influence.
That's true.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to buying souvenirs and stuff.
I want you to teach me.
I want you to teach me a lot.
I want you to tell me a lot.
I want to know a lot of information from you.
Yes, I do.
You'll do it. You'll buy it.
Like, "This is delicious." "This place is famous.
Please.
I failed.
Well then, it looks like the canned goods are almost ready.
That was quick. It's so fast.
I'm turning it.
Let's switch.
I'm going to go now.
See you soon.
I'm off.